I eat a lot of ice cream and here's how
I do it without losing track of my
fitness goals. I use the Ninja Creamy to
make low calorie high protein ice cream
every night and it's still delicious.
Here are the five I made this week.
Started off by testing some new ball
recipes. This is a pumpkin spice latte
ice cream. Then I made a alltime classic
almond joy coconut base with almonds,
chocolate chips, and coconut flakes
mixed in. Then I tried to make a
peppermint frosty like the one Wendy's
had in the winter and it was insane.
This recipe is so easy and it is so so
good. I also tried to recreate the
Portillo's cake shake and this was a
massive success and it packed over 50 g
of protein. Then I made a Captain Crunch
cereal milk ice cream. This was cereal
milk made with Captain Crunch obviously
and then some Captain Crunch bits mixed
in. This one's definitely a little more
work, but it is well well worth it.
Follow me for more recipes like this.